

Horacio Correia

Full Stack Developer

91 421 3861 Sao Miguel, Azores rmcorre@gmail.com



About Me

I'm a Canadian expat with an adventurous spirit and a curiosity for the unknown. These two characteristics have always been strong motivators in my life and have led me to some awesome experiences. Now, prepared to embark on a new journey, I'm itching to begin my next great adventure.

Core Competencies

Concepts

OOP Modeling
RDBMS Patterns
REST Architecture

Technologies

Java JavaScript HTML5 CSS3 SOL

Frameworks / Libraries

Spring Hibernate
Tomcat JUnit
Mockito React
Bootstrap JQuery

Tools

8

Educational Background

Full Stack Web Development Certification
FreeCodeCamp | 2016 - Ongoing
Online

Full Stack Developer
Academia De Codigo | 2019 - 2019
Azores

Curso ABC

Rede Valorizar | 2015 - 2016 Azores

Bachelor of Arts

Concordia University of Edmonton | 1992 - 1995 Canada

Work Experience

Customer Service Representative Tesco | 2016 - 2017

Responsible for assisting customers in addition to:

Stocking, organizing, and labelling shelves Checking product for expiration dates Reducing prices on products due to expire Checkout duties when required

Warehouse Technician

Kuehne + Nagel | 2013 - 2014

Responsible for warehouse transfers to various Best Buy stores in the province of Alberta in addition to:

Preparing daily pick-slips for co-workers
Checking transfers to ensure accuracy
Meeting daily shipping schedules and requirements
Monitoring and organizing inventory for accuracy

Git Webpack
NPM IntelliJ
VSCode Chrome

Loading and unloading trailers and containers